I want to flip A-Train.
Why the fuck would I ever talk to you?
'Cause
you gave Starlight that footage.
Surveillance footage was taken
from Crime Analytics
and given to Starlight.
She just wanted some help...
- She confessed. Leak plugged.
- You don't think
the next word out of her mouth
might've been useful?
My dad's about to die.
I need a dose of Compound V
and I need it today.
What the fuck?
What happens when he finds out
you murdered his family?
- It was me.
- What was you?
I'm so sorry.
I hate you.
Kimiko!
Starlight visited a clinic
and she had an abortion.
Baby killer!
What happened to me back there?
Welcome to Godolkin University.
The virus only affects Supes.
It attaches to the Compound V
in their blood.
Concentrate the dose.
Let's see how sick we can make her.
- Is this all of it?
- Yeah.
You're the only one
who knows how to replicate it.
In a world of chaos.
some things never change.
That good will always win.
That love conquers all.
And that heroes will answer the call
to protect. to inspire.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Welcome to the V52 Expo.
Now please give a big round of applause
for your hosts
Cameron Coleman and The Deep.
Homelander.
- Nice trip home?
- Thank you. Superfans.
We are so excited to be here
with you. celebrating another year...
This turnout.
They love the fuck out of you.
Talk about bread and circus.
...G-Men: World War trilogy.
scheduled for release this summer.
G-Men: World War III.
And it's just one
of the many new projects we've got
- coming to you on the VCU timeline.
- Phases seven through 19.
Which we'll be sharing with you all
today in exhaustive detail.
Are you okay?
Is there anything. like.
buzzing or tingling or... weird?
No. I'm telling you. I feel great.
Are you absolutely sure I had a stroke?
- Yes.
- What's the last thing you remember?
Let me see... I was at Smart & Final.
I was buying a family pack of pizza rolls.
They didn't have pepperoni.
so I had to get supreme.
- Or was it Triple Meat?
- Dad.
No. it was supreme.
I remember it had
the little green pepper specks in it.
Dad! Forget about the fucking pizza rolls.
Well. he sure sounds like himself.
Yeah. I mean. if I was as bad as they
say. then I-I-I shouldn't be alive. right?
I mean. it's a true blue miracle.
Why don't you get some rest?
Okay? Mom and I are gonna go
find you a Diet Snapple.
Okay!
You gave him the V?
Yeah. I thought that's what you wanted.
It fell out of your coat.
I don't understand.
Why did you bring it
if you didn't want to use it?
Look. I wanted to. I...
I did. But then I didn't.
Okay? It's just that I've...
I've seen that shit go wrong
so many times.
Well. it's got to go right
sometimes. right?
I mean. otherwise
there wouldn't be any Supes.
Look at him. He's fine.
Tonight.
on Vought's Funniest Pet Attacks...
Well. um...
You grew up without one parent.
I just couldn't bear
the thought of you losing another one.
Sorry.
Guess Starlight can't decide
whether to rape a baby or kill it.
Well. I am pressing charges for assault.
and that's for damn sure.
And even though the police say
she had an "alibi."
we all know she had
something to do with Ezekiel's murder.
This is a biblical war
of good versus evil. folks.
And I'm declaring hunting season
on Starlighters.
Now. on the subject of baby-killers.
let's welcome our guest
Dr. Dorian Boone.
Dr. Boone. what'd Starlight's baby feel
when she murdered it?
There was a study done
at Samaritan's Embrace University
on ferrets which proves
unborn babies feel pain
as early as conception.
What am I
supposed to do with her
home for two weeks. Marvin?
I have a job.
- So do I.
- And the boy needed stitches.
which you can be sure
we're going to get the bill for.
Suspended for fighting. baby?
This ain't like you.
- Dad. I...
- Uh-uh.
What were you thinking?
He said Homelander's a hero.
so I told him the truth.
Then he told me to f-word off.
so I hit him!
Baby. fighting is not
how you solve problems.
Why not? That's what you do.
Sweetie. go to your room.
Go to your room!
Okay. Monique...
Goddamn it. Marvin.
I am not gonna lose another person I love
to this superhero shit.
Let me talk to her.
You fix this.
Now.
Fuck all this cloak
and dagger shite.
It's bloody freezing out here.
Well. I mean. I was thinking
we could meet in your mom's pussy.
but. you know.
I wanted someplace more private.
- So. what you thinking?
- Butcher. listen.
How about we do this job.
just you and me?
I don't know. Joe.
It's a bit all of a sudden. isn't it?
Billy...
your team is a joke.
You think I haven't noticed?
M.M.'s on the verge of a breakdown.
Frenchie's a fucking junkie.
Hughie is a gaping wet pussy.
And the two Supes on your side?
Man. for whatever reason.
you have a blind spot for them.
All right. I'll give you Starlight.
But Kimiko's a bloody good weapon.
and the rest of them are
still up to scratch.
Well. I don't get you. I don't.
Half your brain is a fucking tumor.
This is your last shot at Homelander.
and now you decide to go soft?
Yeah. they are decent people.
but you and me.
we don't belong with decent.
Hey. so. where is Colin?
Chais pas. Why?
Because he completely ghosted me.
Did you guys
get into a fight or something?
He. uh. went out of town last-minute.
Are you okay?
Super.
How are you?
So great.
Fucking hell.
it's like a morgue in here.
What's with all the long faces?
I don't know. maybe because
I'm getting blamed for the murder you did.
I'd call you a cunt. but you ain't
got the depth or the warmth.
I've been meaning to ask you something.
How was it that you took out Ezekiel?
I have no idea.
- Bullshit.
- God's honest. I. uh...
blacked out. came to. and there he was.
All over the shop.
But never mind that bollocks
because. my son.
I have found it...
the answer to all our prayers.
- And what might that be?
- Ah. it's nothing much.
Just a... a virus that kills Supes.
- Such a thing does not exist.
- Did not exist. Does now.
You see. some clever cunts
over at Godolkin University
cooked up a bug
that latches onto the V
in their bloodstream.
Now. it's completely harmless to humans.
but to Supes?
Fucking diabolical.
So. you shove this shit into me
and Kimiko and we just...
drop dead?
Yep. That's the idea.
Now. it ain't juiced enough
to kill Homelander.
But I reckon we get our hands on some
and try it out on our lovely V.P. elect.
And why the hell are we just
finding out about this shit. Butcher?
There's only one small snag.
When I went to God U to nick it.
Neuman had pipped me to the post.
so we're gonna have to nick it from her.
This is insane and desperate.
Even for you.
Well. insanely desperate's where we are.
don't you think. love?
Okay.
All right. all right. Time out.
Look. if this virus is as dangerous
as Butcher says it is.
do you really want it in Neuman's hands?
No. No. you're right.
All right. then. Then we're sorted.
Oh. uh. uh...
One other tiny little thing.
I need you to get us
one presidential pardon.
Lord. they asked me to join The Seven.
I know I should be happy.
but I'm not sure I'm strong enough
to fight all the sinners.
Will you carry me. Jesus?
Are you... are you there?
That clip is from our new
studio division Vought Faith.
Speaking of faith.
let's all have a moment of silence
for my brother in Christ. Ezekiel.
Adios. amigo.
You. um. you all right?
Still searching for this leak.
Hmm.
Any leads?
Working on it.
But it's got to be someone.
That footage didn't just run itself
out of Crime Analytics. am I right?
Let me know if I can help.
Mm.
For fuck's sakes.
You got fleas or something?
Stay close. Dominic.
This won't take long.
Gentlemen...
- I have pottery class in ten minutes.
- Right.
Would you rather finger
some fucking clay or...
...walk the fuck out of here?
- Fuck. really grateful cunt. isn't he?
- Mm.
- Where's your fucking manners?
- It's not my birthday.
and this is not a gift.
Victoria Neuman has something we need.
Some kind of... virus.
- I have no idea what you mean.
- Come on. Stanny.
You struck me as the type of bloke
what keeps his paws
in all sorts of dirty little pies.
Look. you help us
get this virus from Neuman.
we'll help you get the fuck out of here.
You must be pretty desperate to try
and enlist me in a plot against Victoria.
She is like a daughter to me.
- Yeah. a daughter who sold you out.
- She did what I raised her to do.
You're right.
you taught her how to be a monster.
but not her little girl.
Ah...
You didn't know?
She shot up sweet little Zoe full of V.
Turned her into
a tentacle-mouthed nightmare.
How about we get you out of here.
exonerated and throw in custody of Zoe?
There ain't no better deal.
And you know it.
Got to hand it to him...
cunt knows how to wear a whistle.
This is a bad idea.
Starlight.
- What an unexpected pleasure.
- Hmm.
You know. I've always felt
a certain kinship with you.
- Where we headed?
- West.
Charming.
Do you have a towel
I could place over the seat?
Absolute disaster.
- the-the... our honeymoon.
- It wasn't a disaster.
- Come on! Be serious.
- Acapulco wasn't that bad.
Ugh.
- The honeymoon suite had two twin beds.
- Yeah.
There were people vomiting
at the-the swim-up bar...
and the all-included buffet
seemingly only included salmonella.
If you hated it so much.
why did you buy a timeshare?
- He bought a timeshare.
- 'Cause that guy...
That guy put the hard sell on me.
It'd be great to go back. wouldn't it?
Yeah.
For the food poisoning?
No. to...
just to Acapulco. you know?
To... go to Branson and-and Pigeon Forge.
Oh. Paris.
I have always wanted to go to Paris.
- I never knew that.
- Yeah.
They have this walking tour that goes
to all the spots in The Da Vinci Code.
- Oh. Yeah.
- Imagine that.
Yeah. wow. Wow. I'd. uh...
I'd hate to miss it.
That reminds me.
I want to give you... this.
Hughie. which is my engagement ring
for when you propose to Annie.
Wow. Mom. Uh...
Thank you. that's so sweet.
but I-I don't. I don't know if. um.
I don't know if we're ready.
- like. right now...
- Are you crazy?
- Lock that shit down. you moron.
- Okay.
Thank you.
You know. I can't. um...
you know. change anything. but...
I'm really sor...
I'm really sorry that I missed this.
You know. this.
Me. too.
And look. I-I-I know
you tried to reach out to Hughie.
and I should never have kept you away.
It's...
I'm gonna... I'm gonna go
to the ladies' room.
Oh. you okay?
What is it?
You gave her power of attorney.
- I knew...
- You haven't seen her in years.
Did you think I couldn't handle it?
It's not that.
You remember when Jar Jar got leukemia?
- Yeah.
- Cat wouldn't eat.
and yet somehow still had diarrhea.
and you would not let me put him down.
until he eventually kind of just.
- you know. exploded...
- With blood and shit. Yeah. I remember.
- Right.
- But I was nine.
You are still the same little kid.
You hold on tight to everyone.
And I love you for that. but...
you know. when it came to. uh.
an advanced directive...
Let's just say I didn't want
to end up like Jar Jar.
Hey. where's your mom gone?
Uh. she went to the bathroom. remember?
Yeah.
Yeah. of course.
- You got a nice place.
- I've rarely been.
It's the smell.
But if Victoria wanted to keep
her proclivities quiet.
it'd be here.
What is all this?
I'm as surprised as you are.
What'd you find?
It's what I did not.
See. the labels mark each iteration
of this virus.
Somebody's been running tests. but now...
...it's all gone.
What?
Holy shit.
Fucking bitch.
- Easy.
- Victoria. You're looking well.
You think I wouldn't know the minute
you and your ankle monitor stepped out
of that prison?
I don't recall giving you permission
to turn my rec room into a virology lab.
You brought these assholes here?
- They want to kill me.
- I'm sorry.
Are you upset that I betrayed you?
Oi. knock it off. you two.
This ain't Family Pies.
You have five seconds to tell me
what you did to Sameer.
or I paint this fucking room red.
Who the fuck's Sameer?
Enough.
So. you brought in Sameer.
Smart. That's what I'd have done.
But whatever happened to him.
it wasn't us.
We should find him together.
You're fucking kidding me.
If I'm not mistaken.
you hurt these people.
they expose you as a super-abled killer.
yes?
Then I'm afraid that
we are at a stalemate.
You might as well use their expertise.
At the very least.
- they're effective cannon fodder.
- Thanks.
That's really nice of you.
A story about a hero...
I'm not giving up on you.
and you can't give up on yourself.
...and the boy
he taught to run.
Run faster than that!
- I quit.
- Don't you bail on me!
Get off of me!
You can outrun this life.
or you can run yourself
into an early grave.
Thank you. thank you.
Thank you. thank you. Trust me.
I'm just as excited as you all
for this film. that is...
...so close to my heart.
- Being able to tell this...
- Hey. listen. man.
Call me crazy.
but I'm sensing a little tension here.
Anything wrong?
Yeah. dude.
You fucking reported that I got
shitcanned as head of Crime Analytics.
I'm sorry. but...
Look. I got to take a couple of shots
at the home team now and again.
if I'm gonna appear fair and balanced.
- Look. I'll make a retraction.
- No. It's way too late for that shit.
Noah Baumbach pulled me
from his latest slice-of-life drama.
I'm sorry. man.
I don't know what to say.
You know. it wasn't personal.
Be sure to check me out
in the Vought+ thriller. Double Standard.
which just finished
reshooting its reshoots.
making it the most expensive TV show ever.
So. you know. it's got to be good.
am I right?
A-Train!
For the first time
in Vought's history.
we have two Black heroes in The Seven
and one unspecified.
Yeah. Wow.
Vought proudly supports
and amplifies BIPOC voices.
- Isn't that right. Cameron?
- It sure is. Deep.
Which is why these articulate heroes will
lead Vought's newest diversity initiative.
Black At It.
Some say. "Go woke. go broke."
Well. we say. "Go woke. get yoked."
And as part of our new initiative.
we'll be debuting a new feature.
specifically for our diverse audiences.
Custom digital product placement.
Check this out. here we have a clip
from my three-time
MTV Award winner Rising Tide.
Get this. when a white fan
streams my movie.
they'll see me holding a brand
tailor-made to their tastes.
And then. you know.
if a Black fan streams it.
they'll see a delicious
Vought Imperial Peach Cognac.
Ooh. it's pretty cool.
All right. so. chuffa. chuffa
from Cameron and Deep.
Then we announce Ryan's debut series.
Super School.
- That's the title we went with?
- That was the only thing we got cleared.
Then they're gonna throw to me. right?
For my little "why now" moment.
You know. how I got my inspo
from my time really teaching
the next generation of
super-powered youth.
and then it's go time. baby. right?
That's when you're gonna come out to me.
and we do. like.
a little two-hour Q and A.
Bonnie. you look gorgeous today.
by the way.
Did you get my text?
Yeah.
Right. Is that for us? Listen. tell 'em
we'll be out in like 15. 20. okay?
- Okay.
- All right. cool.
Hey. Ryan. what do you think?
Seriously.
What do you think?
I-I really want to know.
It's just...
- I mean. Super School?
- Hmm.
Why are we doing a teen show. anyway?
Um. 'cause we like money.
If you don't want to do it...
...don't.
Don't do it.
I mean it.
I'm just gonna pop the horns up here
a little bit and play devil's advocate.
We are a month away from shooting.
Built all the sets. I think we bought up
half the sound stages in Toronto.
- Who cares?
- Is this because I jerked it
in front of Minka Kelly? Because.
again. that was just crossed wires.
Hey. guy. what's it gonna take
to get you amped?
Do you want a E.P. credit?
That is done.
You want to get script approval?
- I can make anything sing...
- Give him your black Amex.
What?
You want... You know what?
Why don't you take my whole wallet.
- And the keys to your Jaguar.
- I would love...
to do that.
Ryan. what do you say?
No.
Yeah.
So. you're... you're really not mad at me?
No. I'm proud of you
for speaking your mind.
Ryan...
I've been. uh...
manipulated by people my whole life.
Being told what to say. where to stand.
It-It's like being a slave. only worse.
I did some reflecting.
and I realized that I've been doing
the same thing to you.
But no more.
From now on. no more rules.
For either of us.
We are both emancipated from slavery.
We're free.
Sound good?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
Oh. buddy. I-I don't care
what anyone else thinks but you.
Far as I'm concerned.
this whole planet is empty.
Except for you and me.
As if you don't have 60 more pairs.
Prince Andrew gave me these shoes.
I'm suddenly reminded of
how much I hated it here.
Really? I used to love it.
I always felt a little more free here.
And yet you've turned my farm
- into an infectious disease lab.
- Clear.
I can only assume that you're searching
for a way to control Homelander.
You know. he's a Freudian cesspool
of random impulse and deep insecurity.
There's no one who can control that.
You've put yourself and Zoe
in terrible danger.
No. You put me and Zoe in terrible danger.
You used me like you use everybody else.
Somebody had to protect her.
You mean shooting her up with Compound V.
You took a bright-eyed little girl.
- and you turned her into a...
- Into a what?
A monster?
Is that why you had me hide what I was?
Stick to the shadows.
never reach too high?
- That was to protect you.
- No.
that was because you were ashamed of me.
My daughter will never have to
live like that.
So. what's gonna happen when we find
the virus and this little truce is over?
Starlight blinds the bitch.
before she knows what's what.
- I'll jab her with a dose.
- Okay.
We've got a casualty.
Is that Sameer?
No. it's one of his lab assistants.
What the hell is...
V'd-up fucking chicken!
Fuck this.
Well. you could've warned us
your pal Sameer was V-ing up
a Kentucky Fried fucking massacre.
couldn't ya?
I didn't know. okay?
Something obviously went wrong.
- We have to find him.
- Yeah. right.
And we're supposed to believe you?
You eat. sleep and shit lies. don't you?
Right. 'cause you're such
a paragon of virtue.
You tell your friends about
the deal we made?
Wait. wh-what does that mean?
Said he'd steal all your files you had
on me if I gave him Ryan.
Are you fucking kidding me?
And I didn't go through with it. did I?
Which proves I'm on the level.
When are we gonna learn?
He's never gonna fucking change.
All right. listen.
We got a lot of ground to cover.
so let's just go.
It's an absolute wonder to me
that you've all managed to live this long.
What? I didn't go through with it.
Ooh. that's nice.
Excuse me. Hi.
Did I say you could take out
your vibrating Bluetooth anal beads?
Go pop them back in right now.
- This is an important event.
- Uh-huh.
You really expect me to come onstage
in front of our most loyal fans?
Oh. yeah. I want everyone to know what
a grubby little queef-sniffer you are.
Huh.
I'm sorry. This wasn't
how I was planning to tell you.
but. um. this isn't working out
for me anymore.
I mean. it was one thing when
you were really in charge around here.
but now. I mean...
You...
are dumping me?
I need a dom who's dominating.
You know?
But. uh. I hope we can still be friends.
Hmm. Is this your angry look.
or did Starlight fuck up your face?
You know. if you weren't
Homelander's right-hand bitch.
I'd take you out behind the woodshed
and whup your ass.
Mm. sounds on-brand.
You set me up to get my ass beat.
And you fell for it.
But. hey.
now you don't have to play a victim.
You can really be one.
Y'all just think
I'm stupid poor white trash.
I don't think you're poor.
Underestimate me all you want.
Makes it that much easier to
stick a fucking shiv in your back.
Frenchie okay?
Oh.
Are you okay?
I noticed you're having a little. uh...
projectile dysfunction.
Yeah. you know what?
Why don't you worry about yourself. okay?
I am. You're not much use to us
if your powers are on the fuckin' fritz.
Saw you beat the piss out of
Firecracker on national television.
Don't get me wrong.
I enjoyed the hell out of it. but. um.
don't you think it was a little...
out of control?
We can't lose our cool like that.
We?
Come on. Annie. I'm one of
the only people who does get it.
Dual identities.
I'm still Nadia. You think I don't
want to let her out sometimes?
But I can't. I got to be Neuman.
And. shit. you've been
Starlight for so long.
do you even know who Annie is anymore?
Yeah. you really
got your shit locked down.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Tek-Knight.
It's been a whole year
since my last movie.
so I'd say we're due for a reboot.
No. keep your eyes forward.
Don't let them see us talking.
- Who?
- Sage. Homelander. All of them.
Oh. God. Are you on meth?
Remember when we said
we'd help each other?
The leak wasn't Anika. It was me.
What the fuck?
What the fuck? Are you fucking suicidal?
- Just chill out. Ashley.
- Chill out?
You just made me a fucking accomplice.
you piece of shit.
I took one shit in Homelander's toilet.
I'm not joining
the fucking Rebel Alliance.
I need to tell him.
Hey.
You've done a lot more
than just take a shit.
and we both know that.
We made a deal. so you either help me
get Sage off my jock.
or you go down with me.
The Tek-Knight plumbs
a whole new pit of darkness.
With its soundtrack of Nirvana hits
and a 12-minute sequence
that's entirely pitch-black.
I found it. possibly the only bottle of
Diet Kiwi S...
Where's Dad?
I thought he was with you.
- No?
- No.
Dad?
- Hugh?
- Dad?
Dad?
Hugh?
Dad.
- Hugh?
- Wait. wait. wait. wait.
Just wait here for a second.
Hey. Dad.
How'd that happen?
Oh!
Hughie. what's going on?
I do... I don't know.
I don't know what...
Look. why don't you set that down
and. uh. why don't you...
why don't you come with me.
Who are you?
Dad. it's...
Dad. it's me. It's Hughie.
- Excuse me.
- Uh. ma'am?
Oh. my God. Call security!
Call security! Code red!
Don't be like that.
Hey. let me take you to dinner.
Hey. I'm a nice guy. I promise.
What's... what's happening to me?
Attention please.
There has been a report of an emergency.
Proceed calmly to the nearest exit
and leave the building immediately.
- Dad?
- Hugh?
Oh. fuck.
Hugh?
Dad?
I got to go.
Yeah. wait. wait. Just listen.
I can explain everything. all right?
Why don't... why don't you just. uh.
why don't you just come with us?
I can't. I'm sorry. I got to take Hughie
to the Vought Company Store.
He's saving up for a Tek-Knight doll.
He-he-he calls it an action figure.
but. you know. it's a... it's a doll.
Dad. I'm Hughie.
I'm right here.
You're not Hughie.
He's 11.
Hugh?
Why don't we go back to your room?
- Daphne?
- Yeah.
Wh...
what are you doing here?
You shouldn't be here.
You left.
- But I came back. Remember?
- Yeah.
I did everything for you.
and you looked through me
like I wasn't even there!
You ruined my life.
Hughie's life.
Dad. stop.
Get down on the ground.
Sir?
Wait. Wait.
No! No. don't!
- Let's go.
- Daphne!
Please welcome
the Guardians of Godolkin:
Sam Riordan and Cate Dunlap.
Hey. how long's this thing
supposed to go on for?
Why. big plans tonight?
Nothing much.
just gonna maybe fuck your wife.
Excuse me?
Tabitha. She wants me to swing by
for a late-night muff-dive.
Which'll take forever 'cause
I don't need to come up for air.
I can just breathe
right through her juices.
Enough.
I know about your little closeted
eight-armed hand job machine.
I could cut a package together.
have it on the air by tonight.
- You wouldn't.
- Watch me.
So try and keep it classy. okay?
...starring together
in a hilarious new comedy. Flipped.
I'm a stuck-up sorority girl.
he's a nerd.
but when a gypsy swaps our bodies...
So. what do you want to do?
We could go get some Nathan's Famous.
No. I mean a little more boldly.
I mean. like. big picture.
What do you... want to do?
You're gonna laugh at me.
Mm-mm. No. I won't.
I kind of want to help people.
But not like with fake saves.
like really help.
It's what my mom would want.
That's... amazing.
That's great.
You want to help her?
- Hmm? Yeah?
- Yeah.
- But. I mean...
- Great.
Hey. Adam.
will you send that
lovely young lady over here. please?
And you come. too.
Um...
...is he making you uncomfortable?
- Uh...
- No. you can tell me.
You won't get in trouble.
Um...
Kind of.
Yeah.
Ryan?
What do you think?
Adam. I think you should apologize.
Uh. I'm sorry if I was inappropriate.
Didn't seem like you meant it.
Uh. yeah. that's just...
that's just my natural tone.
Maybe the problem is that
Adam is looking down on the P.A.
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
Yeah. um...
Adam. I think you should
get on your knees and do it again.
I'm sorry if I
exploited our inequitable power dynamic.
and I made you feel uncomfortable.
Please forgive me.
- He's still lying.
- Mm-hmm. I agree.
I think maybe he needs to be
taught a lesson.
I want you to slap him.
Bonnie...
Oh! Oh. fuck.
Do it again.
Okay...
- Again.
- Homelander...
Oh! Fuck me.
I'm sorry. Stop. please.
Bonnie. please. Please!
Homelander. pl...
Please. can we take a break?
- Are you all right?
- Yes. I'm all right.
Right.
I didn't know you were a Catholic.
Something about the drama of it appeals.
You know?
Do you still believe in God?
I want to.
It's just. uh...
It's just so hard sometimes.
And you?
With all my heart.
The trinity. the resurrection.
the sacraments... all of it.
Well. except for
the Sacraments of Penance.
Come on.
What a steaming pile of dog shit that is.
I really kind of think that
forgiving is...
- is important.
- Forgiving. oui.
But not being forgiven.
What. I confess to some priest
I don't even know in a peep show booth.
and all my sins wash away?
Dog shit.
Some sins God should not forgive.
Some sins deserve eternal damnation.
Frenchie...
...what have you done?
It is not just one thing. you see.
It is so many things.
You should really talk to someone.
You should. I mean. have you told Kimiko?
If I tell her...
...I'm scared she'll hate me.
I'm even more scared she won't.
Is that a fucking V'd-up bull?
Oh. my God.
Off we fuck. nice and slow.
This is fucking crazy.
Run!
Come on. Go!
Oh. my God.
Come on.
Let's go!
Oh. mon Dieu.
I can't believe this is fucking happening
to me again.
Oh. my God. Sameer.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
I'm fine. but. uh. Henry...
Wait. Zoe's not here. is she?
- Because... No?
- No. no. She's okay. She's okay.
- Okay. good.
- Wait. Oh. my God.
is that Zoe's dad?
Dr. Shah was my top man
at Vought R&D
before he went behind my back
and deflowered my daughter.
Okay. I was 20. thoroughly deflowered.
and this isn't the time or the place.
What happened?
We gave. uh. V to a hamster.
so we could test the virus on it.
Oh. a V'd-up hamster
was your first mistake. mon ami.
It got loose. Trashed the lab. We ran.
but the V had already leaked
into the ground water.
Is the virus gone?
Yes.
Fuck.
Except for. uh...
Except for one dose.
Okay.
Hey.
- How transmissible is that?
- Not very.
Only through bodily fluid.
Blood. saliva... semen.
Okay. so we inject it into your dead buddy
over here as bait.
and then we put him outside to infect
the crazy fucking flying sheep.
This man is in no condition
to fuck a sheep.
They would eat him.
- Oh.
- Bollocks.
That's the only dose.
I say we fucking leg it.
- Butcher's right. it's too valuable.
- Okay. we run.
- we don't all make it.
- Darwinism. love.
Don't got to be the fastest.
just not the slowest.
No fucking way.
- Enough. Not now.
- I won't be able to outrun them.
Oh. don't you cry for that cunt.
He's just trying to nick Zoe from you.
That's his whole fucking plan. isn't it?
He's lying.
- Sorry. Stanny. Just business.
- Guys. stop.
- Son of a bitch.
- I should've fucking known.
M.M. could die. okay? Or Frenchie.
I mean. you really don't care
who you just throw to the wolves?
- No. not really.
- You're a monster.
- and I'm not letting you do this.
- Or what?
You gonna go stark raving
like you did with Firecracker?
I got the head popper
and you can't even get it up.
Enough. Enough! Look. Look.
Y'all see this?
Hives.
And I got them
because y'all motherfuckers
are driving me the fuck crazy.
Now. Annie.
you can't just go around
fucking everybody up.
And. Neuman. do you really
want to risk Zoe growing up
in a group home the way you did?
And you.
Look.
My little baby girl needs me.
and I intend on seeing her.
You're not a monster. Butcher.
You are a motherfucker.
but you a motherfucker with a heart.
He killed those people.
He... Those people.
Yeah. crazy shit happens
when you give healthy people V.
so I guess when someone's brain-dead...
H-How are you so calm?
This sort of isn't the first time
I've been through something like this.
- What are you looking for?
- I don't know. Tobramycin.
topotecan. anything we can use
to maybe slow Dad down.
Wait. w-what if we can't?
Nothing is gonna happen to you.
Daphne!
You... you left me.
- You left our little boy.
- Dad.
- You broke our hearts.
- Dad. stop.
Hugh. please.
Hugh. Hugh. please. Please. Hugh. please.
I'm Hughie. Dad.
I'm the one you took to the Vought Store
to buy the Tek-Knight doll.
Remember. I-I was.
I was short eight bucks.
even though I saved for weeks.
And you said.
"Anything for your number one hero."
But that's the thing. Dad.
he-he-he never was.
You are.
You're my hero.
And that's why I-I needed you to wake up.
so that I could say it. and I. and I.
and I know that you heard it.
You're my hero. Dad.
Hughie?
Yeah. Yeah. Dad. it's me. it's me.
It's Hughie.
W-Where are we?
Oh!
Oh. God. w... Oh. God.
W-Why am I...
I-I don't know what's going on.
- It's-it's a long story. but...
- No! No!
Dad?
Dad. it's Hughie. It's Hughie. remember?
I know. I-I know.
I just. I-I don't...
There's-there's something wrong with me.
I-I can't stop it.
I don't know what to do.
That's okay.
I think I do.
How long did you say it takes
for the virus to kick in?
It's been different every time.
That's not good.
Shit.
Go. go. go! Go. go. go!
Oh!
Oh. shit.
Where's Sameer?
Sameer?
Sameer!
- Victoria. Victoria. Calm down. Just...
- Sameer! Sameer! Where's Sameer?
Where is he?
We don't know...
No. where is he? No. where's Sameer?
Not very sporting of you
to renege on a deal.
Deal was a pardon for the virus. No virus?
No deal.
We scoured the property.
We couldn't find Dr. Shah.
but we did find this.
- Thank you.
- I'm very sorry.
Hmm.
Jesus fucking Christ. are you serious?
Shh.
What does it mean to be a hero?
This country is corrupt beyond repair.
So. we got to save it.
We have to save America.
We have to save the world for our kids.
So. I'm reaching out to you.
to do your part.
Now. it's not gonna be easy. We'll...
We'll have to do some terrible things.
Some violent.
merciless. maybe even cruel things.
for the greater good.
That's war.
You'll no longer be beloved celebrities.
You will be wrathful gods.
When the time comes...
...will you answer the call?
How will we know when the time comes?
Trust me. you'll know.
Anything you need. Homelander.
You see. we recently found a leak
here at Vought Tower. and I thought.
together. we might plug it.
The proof was on his phone.
Calls to Marvin Milk.
I don't know who that is.
I don't know who Marvin Milk is.
I didn't do it. This is a mistake.
Someone set me up.
I didn't do anything.
So...
A-Train.
Show me a little wrath.
I'm still gonna fuck your wife tonight.
Not here.
Hello.
Uh. just a moment. sir.
Madame. excusez-moi.
- Sir. we'll get to you when we can...
- I have committed murders.
Plural.
There's a 10-13 at the front desk.
Sir. please put your hands
where I can see them.
How do you know this is even gonna work?
I-I have this. uh. French friend.
He kind of taught me
way too much about drugs.
Look. if we don't do this.
then he spends the rest of his life
scared and confused. in-in prison
or-or an asylum.
Or he kills more innocent people.
He's right.
Hughie's right.
I don't want to be Jar Jar.
It's not gonna hurt.
Thank you.
For taking such good care of our boy.
I promise I will do the same.
Yeah.
W-Wh...
What's happening?
- I feel...
- Okay.
I'm-I'm-I'm scared.
Hey. hey. Dad. it's okay.
Hey. I'm right here.
I'm right here. We both are.
And I-I love you so much.
I'm not gonna hold on. okay? You can go.
I love you. too. son.
My wee Hughie.
Oh. y-you know where I really want to go?
- Where?
- Is Paris.
Uh. yeah. Yeah. you know. we can...
three of us. we can do
the Da Vinci Code tour.
- Oh. yeah. The three of us.
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- The three of us.
Visit all those... those spots where...
Tom... Tom Hanks...
It's okay.
Now. see?
That is classic Butcher.
You get away from me! Get away from me!
All right. take it easy.
I ain't gonna hurt you.
Well. not no more.
It was just enough to convince people.
- You chopped off my fucking leg.
- Yes. I did.
I ain't gonna sugarcoat it.
your football days are over.
but don't you worry.
we'll patch you up.
right as rain.
and you'll be back to work in no time.
Work? What work?
Well. what the fuck do you think?
You're gonna make us
some more of that virus.
No. no...
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm